Accounting, Office of; Records ua351
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Office of Accounting Records
1967 - 1983
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua351
0.33 cubic ft.
61 captures
The collection consists of inactive records from the University at Albany's Office of Accounting.
Collection X
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Arrangement of the Collection
Physical items in the collection were maintained in the original order after transfer.
Administrative History
The University at Albany's Office of Accounting establishes policies and procedures associated with the University's fiscal transactions. The Office publishes guidelines for University employees on the use of university funds and offers guidance on travel reimbursement.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of departmental accounting and expense reports, memoranda on claims and billing procedures, manuals for travel procedure, reports and memoranda from the Office of Sponsored Funds, and the annual Chart of Accounts, 1971-1980. The collection also contains web-captures of the Office of Accounting's website from 2004 to the present.
State University of New York at Albany-Administration; Web Archives; UAlbany Finance & Business; Wages -- New York (State)
- Accounting Office Website, 2004 April 12 - 2017 May 17; 1; 61 captures
  URL
  http://www.albany.edu/accounting/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: University at Albany, SUNY Website
  created_date: 2012-09-17T13:15:00Z
  created_by: bkeough
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:05Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2004 April 12
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2004 June 4
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2004 October 18
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2005 March 10
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2005 April 8
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2005 August 28
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2005 September 17
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2005 September 24
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2005 December 3
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2006 September 1
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2007 January 10
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2007 February 22
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2007 June 7
  - University at Albany: Accounting, 2008 April 29
  - Accounting, 2008 June 29
  - Accounting, 2009 January 26
  - Accounting, 2009 February 2
  - Accounting, 2010 February 17
  - Accounting, 2012 April 19
  - Accounting, 2012 June 23
  - Accounting, 2012 July 1
  - Accounting, 2012 December 1
  - Accounting, 2012 December 31
  - Accounting, 2013 April 1
  - Accounting, 2013 May 8
    This item had no crawl rules.
    The CDX index for this capture did not contain crawl information.
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2013 May 8
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - Accounting, 2013 September 11
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2013 September 11
  - Accounting, 2013 October 1
  - Internet Archive Wayback Machine, 2013 November 13
  - WARC file for Internet Archive Wayback Machine, 2013 November 13
  - Accounting, 2014 May 3
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2014 May 3
  - Accounting, 2014 May 14
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2014 May 14
  - Accounting, 2014 August 27
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2014 August 27
  - Accounting, 2014 September 17
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2014 September 17
  - Accounting, 2015 July 17
    crawl: 165088
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2015-07-22T22:02:18Z
    end_date: 2015-07-22T21:28:19Z
    elapsed_ms: 448383534
    Crawl Types
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    pdfs_only: False
    test: False
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 432000
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 518483
    novel_count: 22064
    duplicate_count: 310947
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 185472
    downloaded_count: 333011
    download_failures: 280
    warc_revisit_count: 310940
    warc_url_count: 332912
    total_data_in_kbs: 92321075
    duplicate_bytes: 89386949991
    warc_compressed_bytes: 975896456
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.74
    kb_rate: 205.0
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2015 July 17
  - Accounting, 2015 December 17
    crawl: 187970
    start_date: 2015-12-17T16:55:04Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-17T16:55:04Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-22T21:57:26Z
    end_date: 2015-12-22T21:40:44Z
    elapsed_ms: 449129872
    discovered_count: 304232
    novel_count: 13877
    duplicate_count: 191764
    queued_count: 98591
    downloaded_count: 205641
    download_failures: 234
    warc_revisit_count: 191759
    warc_url_count: 205547
    total_data_in_kbs: 60257781
    duplicate_bytes: 60588343215
    warc_compressed_bytes: 34726906
    doc_rate: 0.46
    kb_rate: 134.0
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2015 December 17
  - Accounting, 2016 March 17
    crawl: 201840
    Crawl Rules
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ualbanysports.com (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for library.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for asrc.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for atmos.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for bioinformatics.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cela.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for choose.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cs.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for csda.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for imls.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cwig.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for events.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for hr.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for ibl.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for illiad.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for liblogs.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for libguides.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for scholarsarchive.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for listserv.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for m.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for omega.math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for mumford.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for nyjm.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for pdp.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for resnet.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cyberphysics.rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rna.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for slsc.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uaems.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uapps.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for wiki.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-22T18:02:10Z
    end_date: 2016-03-22T16:56:57Z
    elapsed_ms: 432107388
    discovered_count: 639552
    novel_count: 138564
    duplicate_count: 332568
    queued_count: 168420
    downloaded_count: 471132
    download_failures: 1411433
    warc_revisit_count: 332563
    warc_url_count: 471037
    total_data_in_kbs: 116820623
    duplicate_bytes: 113225737713
    warc_compressed_bytes: 765920585
    doc_rate: 1.09
    kb_rate: 270.0
  - WARC file for Accounting, 2016 March 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 May 17
    crawl: 212937
    start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-24T10:38:52Z
    end_date: 2016-05-22T22:20:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 451503421
    discovered_count: 8685839
    novel_count: 568136
    duplicate_count: 1043240
    queued_count: 7074463
    downloaded_count: 1611376
    download_failures: 229
    warc_revisit_count: 1043205
    warc_url_count: 1611247
    total_data_in_kbs: 246906729
    duplicate_bytes: 230750229955
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2352496320
    doc_rate: 3.57
    kb_rate: 546.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 May 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
    crawl: 231044
    Block host dev.library.albany.edu
    start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-23T01:20:50Z
    end_date: 2016-08-22T23:33:45Z
    elapsed_ms: 455703830
    discovered_count: 1189467
    novel_count: 184079
    duplicate_count: 736427
    queued_count: 268961
    downloaded_count: 920506
    download_failures: 267
    warc_revisit_count: 736404
    warc_url_count: 920384
    total_data_in_kbs: 202254345
    duplicate_bytes: 198029314926
    warc_compressed_bytes: 397770039
    doc_rate: 2.02
    kb_rate: 443.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 December 17
    crawl: 255339
    start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-22T23:02:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-22T17:39:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 434651176
    discovered_count: 5605147
    novel_count: 672626
    duplicate_count: 721586
    queued_count: 4210935
    downloaded_count: 1394212
    download_failures: 247
    warc_revisit_count: 721559
    warc_url_count: 1394095
    total_data_in_kbs: 173161585
    duplicate_bytes: 152072050167
    warc_compressed_bytes: 4226018506
    doc_rate: 3.21
    kb_rate: 398.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 December 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
    crawl: 261028
    start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-23T00:48:05Z
    end_date: 2017-01-22T19:31:33Z
    elapsed_ms: 440845477
    discovered_count: 6856243
    novel_count: 810250
    duplicate_count: 844972
    queued_count: 5201021
    downloaded_count: 1655222
    download_failures: 351
    warc_revisit_count: 844920
    warc_url_count: 1655090
    total_data_in_kbs: 260833049
    duplicate_bytes: 210669517964
    warc_compressed_bytes: 15598206209
    doc_rate: 3.75
    kb_rate: 591.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 February 17
    crawl: 267806
    start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-22T23:52:19Z
    end_date: 2017-02-22T17:57:15Z
    elapsed_ms: 435595208
    discovered_count: 6181071
    novel_count: 757736
    duplicate_count: 820126
    queued_count: 4603209
    downloaded_count: 1577862
    download_failures: 339
    warc_revisit_count: 820090
    warc_url_count: 1577729
    total_data_in_kbs: 257873727
    duplicate_bytes: 232995142726
    warc_compressed_bytes: 5661819855
    doc_rate: 3.62
    kb_rate: 592.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 February 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
    crawl: 273971
    start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T22:25:00Z
    end_date: 2017-03-22T18:08:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 436406787
    discovered_count: 7409222
    novel_count: 690900
    duplicate_count: 1257496
    queued_count: 5460826
    downloaded_count: 1948396
    download_failures: 359
    warc_revisit_count: 1257455
    warc_url_count: 1948270
    total_data_in_kbs: 266864045
    duplicate_bytes: 245675593330
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1581675727
    doc_rate: 4.46
    kb_rate: 611.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 April 17
    crawl: 291352
    start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-22T22:22:12Z
    end_date: 2017-04-22T17:55:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 435220728
    discovered_count: 8221578
    novel_count: 736180
    duplicate_count: 1311488
    queued_count: 6173910
    downloaded_count: 2047668
    download_failures: 335
    warc_revisit_count: 1311435
    warc_url_count: 2047538
    total_data_in_kbs: 284745035
    duplicate_bytes: 261915565851
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2411311996
    doc_rate: 4.7
    kb_rate: 654.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 April 17
  - Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
    crawl: 301465
    Host Rule Type C CONTAINS meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search? (last updated 2017-05-11)
    start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-23T00:29:43Z
    end_date: 2017-05-22T21:46:25Z
    elapsed_ms: 449440076
    discovered_count: 2923335
    novel_count: 388249
    duplicate_count: 1238165
    queued_count: 1296921
    downloaded_count: 1626414
    download_failures: 336
    warc_revisit_count: 1238113
    warc_url_count: 1626286
    total_data_in_kbs: 265327774
    duplicate_bytes: 251274786133
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3306915146
    kb_rate: 590.0
  - WARC file for Accounting Office - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
- Administrative Records, 1967-1983; 2; 0.33 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Collection was maintained in the original order after it was transferred.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of departmental accounting reports, memoranda on claims and billing procedures, departmental expense reports, manuals for travel procedure, reports and memoranda from the Office of Sponsored Funds, and the annual Chart of Accounts, 1971-1980.
  The collections consists of memoranda on accounting practices, 1970-83, the Office of Sponsored Funds, 1975-82, progress reports on Sponsored Funds, 1967-69, and a chart of accounts, 1971-80.